Marvis Ijenwa

in marvis-ijenwa () IjEmpire 🔰 IJ_Empire k Kaggle-ijEmpire

Profile

An economist, a mathematician and a front-end web developer competent in building static, interactive and/or responsive websites, web as well as mobile applications with technologies such as html, css, sass, bootstrap, javascript, react, php among others. Adept at working with people and in teams, possesses uncompromising ethics, resilient and transparent communication skills, and consistently showcases the ability to analyze issues, recognize problems, and draw logical solutions.

Skills			
• HTML	• Sass/Scss	Resposnsive Web Design	
• CSS	 Bootstrap 	• React JS	
• React Native	• Git	• Data Analysis	
 Javascript 	 Microsoft office 	Python	
• Research	• Sales	 Business communication 	
Education			
2011	GCE, Staff Model Secondary School, College of Education, Agbor		
2015	BSc Finance, Caritas University, Amorji-Nike, Enugu		
2022	MSc Economics, Friedrich Schiller Universität, Jena		

Languages

• English	• Ika	• German
LIIGUSII	ma	ocimun

• Igbo Hausa

Certificates

 HTML Linkedin Skill 	 CSS Linkedin Skill Assessment 	 Javascript Linkedin Skill
Assessment Badge	Badge	Assessment Badge

Interests

• Writing Philosophy Cycling

Organisations

2010 – 2018	Roayal Ambassadors, Youth and Lifestyle Coach	Delta, Nigeria
2016 – 2017	NYSC, Community Development Worker	Katsina, Nigeria

Professional Experience

Quality Control Specialist, Amazon Logistics Erfurt, Germany Sep 2021 – Feb 2022 • Developed and performed quality test processes. Made recommendations for repairing defects. • Maintained working knowledge of quality standards. May 2016 - Apr 2017 **Mathematics & Computer Science Teacher,** Batagarawa, **National Youth Service Corps** Katsina, Nigeria • Preparing maths lesson plans as per the grade levels. • Developing students' interest in mathematics. • Giving projects and assignments to the students. • Facilitating classroom discussions on various topics. • Building a strong relationship with the students. Jan 2011 - Apr 2015 M.N & Sons Enterprises Agbor, Nigeria Accounting • Sales

Purchasing